Warning!
Using this program exempt creator from liability for your account!
If you agree that you use it only at your own risk, press Enter:
You play on the off. server osu! Bancho? Enter y / n:
Enter the IP address or DNS address of the IRC server where you playing:
Enter the port of the IRC server (by default 6667):
ATTENTION! For using the application DOES NOT NEED YOUR ACCOUNT PASSWORD!
You should get a special IRC password at https://osu.ppy.sh/p/irc
Enter your osu! login:
Enter your IRC (!!!!) password:
Attempting to connect to the specified server...
Connection successful! Online flooder starts to work, enjoy the reaction of your friends ;3
Close this window when you want to stop flooding.
Check username or password!